var jsonMovement = `{
  "id": 106,
  "title": "Movement",
  "clues": [{
      "id": 7000,
      "answer": "Pace",
      "question": "A 2 beat, lateral gait",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7001,
      "answer": "3",
      "question": "The number of beats in a canter",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7002,
      "answer": "4",
      "question": "The number of beats in a gallop",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7003,
      "answer": "4",
      "question": "The number of beats in a walk",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7004,
      "answer": "2",
      "question": "The number of beats in a trot",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7005,
      "answer": "Stride",
      "question": "The distance and/or time from when a particular foot leaves the ground until that foot strikes the ground again",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7006,
      "answer": "Walk",
      "question": "This gait is characterized by a slow, naturally flat-footed, four beat gait. It is also known as the foundation gait",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7007,
      "answer": "Cadence",
      "question": "Judging term refers to the ability of the horse to maintain a correct and distinct foot fall pattern",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7008,
      "answer": "Jog",
      "question": "The term for the slow, smooth, trot of a western horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 7009,
      "answer": "Walk",
      "question": "The slowest gait of a horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 106,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    }
  ]
}`;
